

□ (+1) 847-708-5444 | Soeybatts00@yahoo.com | A Tusk00.github.io | In JBattista00



Summary _

Highly motivated computer science student currently at Triton college (3.6 GPA) seeking to use my development experience at an entry-level job. I have been programming for about 2 years with various languages. I'm skilled with C++, Python, and have used some java, and some HTML. I love coding random projects in my free time, my most recent project was a remake of the game asteroids using pygame.

Education _

Triton College 2000 5th Ave, River Grove, IL

A.S in Programming/Game Development 2019-2022

Southern Illinois University of Edwardsville

35 Circle Dr, Edwardsville, IL Water/Wastewater Operator 2018-2019

Work Experience _

Norridge Park District 4631 N Overhill Ave, Norridge, IL FRONT DESK REGISTRAR Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

- · Managing the district fitness center
- Taking registrations for classes
- Taking sign ins for classes and gym
- · Cleaning and sanitation of the gym

City of Elmhurst 985 S Riverside Dr, Elmhurst, IL

PUBLIC WORKS INTERN May 2019 - Aug 2019

- Lab Tests(Ph, Alkalinity, Oxygen Demand, etc)
- Collecting samples
- · Fixing main breaks
- · Checking sewer lines with RC camera
- Clearing sewer lines

Skills .

Soft Skills

• PROBLEM SOLVING, ADAPTABILITY, COLLABORATION, COMMUNICATION,

Computer Science

•PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE: PYTHON, C++, JAVA

•DATABASE: SQL SERVER

Awards _

Presidents Honors List Triton College

AWARDED TO STUDENTS WITH A 3.75 GPA OR HIGHER 2019 - 2021